sets = [
    {
        "grade": 1,
        "questions": [
            {"question": "24 + 1", "answer": "25"},
            {"question": "76 + 9", "answer": "85"},
            {"question": "20 + 46", "answer": "66"},
            {"question": "94 + 4", "answer": "98"},
            {"question": "94 + 5", "answer": "99"},
            {"question": "19 + 70", "answer": "89"},
            {"question": "35 + 44", "answer": "79"},
            {"question": "44 + 52", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "25 + 4", "answer": "29"},
            {"question": "53 + 30", "answer": "83"},
            {"question": "94 + 1", "answer": "95"},
            {"question": "60 + 36", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "71 + 7", "answer": "78"},
            {"question": "51 + 25", "answer": "76"},
            {"question": "49 + 46", "answer": "95"},
            {"question": "29 + 15", "answer": "44"},
            {"question": "68 + 9", "answer": "77"},
            {"question": "78 + 9", "answer": "87"},
            {"question": "19 + 70", "answer": "89"},
            {"question": "31 + 12", "answer": "43"},
            {"question": "13 + 58", "answer": "71"},
            {"question": "4 + 12", "answer": "16"},
            {"question": "23 + 15", "answer": "38"},
            {"question": "22 + 10", "answer": "32"},
            {"question": "92 + 1", "answer": "93"},
            {"question": "94 + 3", "answer": "97"},
            {"question": "22 + 74", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "65 + 3", "answer": "68"},
            {"question": "96 + 1", "answer": "97"},
            {"question": "98 + 1", "answer": "99"},
            {"question": "34 + 34", "answer": "68"},
            {"question": "46 + 3", "answer": "49"},
            {"question": "54 + 33", "answer": "87"},
            {"question": "90 + 8", "answer": "98"},
            {"question": "35 + 25", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "63 + 16", "answer": "79"},
            {"question": "16 + 50", "answer": "66"},
            {"question": "78 + 18", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "53 + 38", "answer": "91"},
            {"question": "26 + 55", "answer": "81"},
            {"question": "90 + 3", "answer": "93"},
            {"question": "62 + 2", "answer": "64"},
            {"question": "55 + 33", "answer": "88"},
            {"question": "38 + 58", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "29 + 30", "answer": "59"},
            {"question": "64 + 11", "answer": "75"},
            {"question": "84 + 7", "answer": "91"},
            {"question": "49 + 21", "answer": "70"},
            {"question": "86 + 3", "answer": "89"},
            {"question": "10 + 87", "answer": "97"},
            {"question": "38 - 34", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "96 - 6", "answer": "90"},
            {"question": "62 - 42", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "11 - 1", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "91 - 32", "answer": "59"},
            {"question": "5 - 3", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "23 - 10", "answer": "13"},
            {"question": "11 - 9", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "37 - 14", "answer": "23"},
            {"question": "31 - 11", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "35 - 28", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "34 - 14", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "93 - 65", "answer": "28"},
            {"question": "47 - 39", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "34 - 5", "answer": "29"},
            {"question": "49 - 43", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "80 - 6", "answer": "74"},
            {"question": "43 - 9", "answer": "34"},
            {"question": "66 - 32", "answer": "34"},
            {"question": "55 - 37", "answer": "18"},
            {"question": "51 - 24", "answer": "27"},
            {"question": "33 - 10", "answer": "23"},
            {"question": "17 - 7", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "43 - 28", "answer": "15"},
            {"question": "64 - 53", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "43 - 15", "answer": "28"},
            {"question": "43 - 6", "answer": "37"},
            {"question": "66 - 49", "answer": "17"},
            {"question": "72 - 18", "answer": "54"},
            {"question": "99 - 97", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "25 - 19", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "39 - 24", "answer": "15"},
            {"question": "39 - 9", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "95 - 46", "answer": "49"},
            {"question": "72 - 12", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "76 - 30", "answer": "46"},
            {"question": "75 - 12", "answer": "63"},
            {"question": "92 - 40", "answer": "52"},
            {"question": "68 - 61", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "45 - 30", "answer": "15"},
            {"question": "84 - 72", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "49 - 43", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "12 - 3", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "54 - 4", "answer": "50"},
            {"question": "14 - 13", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "25 - 6", "answer": "19"},
            {"question": "76 - 3", "answer": "73"},
            {"question": "82 - 4", "answer": "78"},
            {"question": "26 - 25", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "33 - 11", "answer": "22"},
        ],
    },
    {
        "grade": 2,
        "questions": [
            {"question": "333 + 241", "answer": "574"},
            {"question": "567 + 271", "answer": "838"},
            {"question": "153 + 601", "answer": "754"},
            {"question": "547 + 173", "answer": "720"},
            {"question": "547 + 189", "answer": "736"},
            {"question": "515 + 266", "answer": "781"},
            {"question": "568 + 271", "answer": "839"},
            {"question": "503 + 153", "answer": "656"},
            {"question": "530 + 286", "answer": "816"},
            {"question": "599 + 143", "answer": "742"},
            {"question": "788 + 185", "answer": "973"},
            {"question": "146 + 103", "answer": "249"},
            {"question": "670 + 169", "answer": "839"},
            {"question": "246 + 116", "answer": "362"},
            {"question": "108 + 460", "answer": "568"},
            {"question": "259 + 177", "answer": "436"},
            {"question": "774 + 112", "answer": "886"},
            {"question": "407 + 383", "answer": "790"},
            {"question": "194 + 380", "answer": "574"},
            {"question": "263 + 587", "answer": "850"},
            {"question": "716 + 128", "answer": "844"},
            {"question": "522 + 326", "answer": "848"},
            {"question": "654 + 312", "answer": "966"},
            {"question": "748 + 174", "answer": "922"},
            {"question": "484 + 204", "answer": "688"},
            {"question": "337 + 464", "answer": "801"},
            {"question": "128 + 196", "answer": "324"},
            {"question": "433 + 221", "answer": "654"},
            {"question": "170 + 724", "answer": "894"},
            {"question": "789 + 120", "answer": "909"},
            {"question": "530 + 431", "answer": "961"},
            {"question": "351 + 405", "answer": "756"},
            {"question": "786 + 162", "answer": "948"},
            {"question": "700 + 241", "answer": "941"},
            {"question": "512 + 282", "answer": "794"},
            {"question": "597 + 221", "answer": "818"},
            {"question": "512 + 344", "answer": "856"},
            {"question": "376 + 609", "answer": "985"},
            {"question": "337 + 502", "answer": "839"},
            {"question": "269 + 131", "answer": "400"},
            {"question": "652 + 126", "answer": "778"},
            {"question": "486 + 330", "answer": "816"},
            {"question": "716 + 180", "answer": "896"},
            {"question": "437 + 413", "answer": "850"},
            {"question": "400 + 488", "answer": "888"},
            {"question": "771 + 163", "answer": "934"},
            {"question": "789 + 190", "answer": "979"},
            {"question": "219 + 626", "answer": "845"},
            {"question": "733 + 155", "answer": "888"},
            {"question": "621 + 122", "answer": "743"},
            {"question": "907 - 571", "answer": "336"},
            {"question": "863 - 698", "answer": "165"},
            {"question": "434 - 175", "answer": "259"},
            {"question": "717 - 357", "answer": "360"},
            {"question": "320 - 115", "answer": "205"},
            {"question": "707 - 541", "answer": "166"},
            {"question": "705 - 538", "answer": "167"},
            {"question": "466 - 277", "answer": "189"},
            {"question": "805 - 152", "answer": "653"},
            {"question": "702 - 669", "answer": "33"},
            {"question": "219 - 175", "answer": "44"},
            {"question": "463 - 141", "answer": "322"},
            {"question": "451 - 368", "answer": "83"},
            {"question": "989 - 268", "answer": "721"},
            {"question": "343 - 245", "answer": "98"},
            {"question": "572 - 500", "answer": "72"},
            {"question": "721 - 527", "answer": "194"},
            {"question": "424 - 394", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "267 - 134", "answer": "133"},
            {"question": "126 - 101", "answer": "25"},
            {"question": "547 - 130", "answer": "417"},
            {"question": "734 - 580", "answer": "154"},
            {"question": "496 - 267", "answer": "229"},
            {"question": "959 - 588", "answer": "371"},
            {"question": "547 - 131", "answer": "416"},
            {"question": "860 - 179", "answer": "681"},
            {"question": "477 - 305", "answer": "172"},
            {"question": "832 - 577", "answer": "255"},
            {"question": "331 - 284", "answer": "47"},
            {"question": "406 - 322", "answer": "84"},
            {"question": "907 - 816", "answer": "91"},
            {"question": "801 - 520", "answer": "281"},
            {"question": "969 - 677", "answer": "292"},
            {"question": "351 - 193", "answer": "158"},
            {"question": "777 - 325", "answer": "452"},
            {"question": "837 - 524", "answer": "313"},
            {"question": "374 - 289", "answer": "85"},
            {"question": "587 - 524", "answer": "63"},
            {"question": "755 - 458", "answer": "297"},
            {"question": "654 - 425", "answer": "229"},
            {"question": "809 - 251", "answer": "558"},
            {"question": "354 - 238", "answer": "116"},
            {"question": "790 - 109", "answer": "681"},
            {"question": "775 - 589", "answer": "186"},
            {"question": "405 - 173", "answer": "232"},
            {"question": "458 - 327", "answer": "131"},
            {"question": "954 - 927", "answer": "27"},
            {"question": "532 - 259", "answer": "273"},
            {"question": "925 - 343", "answer": "582"},
            {"question": "976 - 354", "answer": "622"},
        ],
    },
    {
        "grade": 3,
        "questions": [
            {"question": "1 * 1", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "1 * 2", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "1 * 3", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "1 * 4", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "1 * 5", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "1 * 6", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "1 * 7", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "1 * 8", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "1 * 9", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "1 * 10", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "1 * 11", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "1 * 12", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "2 * 1", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "2 * 2", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "2 * 3", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "2 * 4", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "2 * 5", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "2 * 6", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "2 * 7", "answer": "14"},
            {"question": "2 * 8", "answer": "16"},
            {"question": "2 * 9", "answer": "18"},
            {"question": "2 * 10", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "2 * 11", "answer": "22"},
            {"question": "2 * 12", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "3 * 1", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "3 * 2", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "3 * 3", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "3 * 4", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "3 * 5", "answer": "15"},
            {"question": "3 * 6", "answer": "18"},
            {"question": "3 * 7", "answer": "21"},
            {"question": "3 * 8", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "3 * 9", "answer": "27"},
            {"question": "3 * 10", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "3 * 11", "answer": "33"},
            {"question": "3 * 12", "answer": "36"},
            {"question": "4 * 1", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "4 * 2", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "4 * 3", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "4 * 4", "answer": "16"},
            {"question": "4 * 5", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "4 * 6", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "4 * 7", "answer": "28"},
            {"question": "4 * 8", "answer": "32"},
            {"question": "4 * 9", "answer": "36"},
            {"question": "4 * 10", "answer": "40"},
            {"question": "4 * 11", "answer": "44"},
            {"question": "4 * 12", "answer": "48"},
            {"question": "5 * 1", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "5 * 2", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "5 * 3", "answer": "15"},
            {"question": "5 * 4", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "5 * 5", "answer": "25"},
            {"question": "5 * 6", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "5 * 7", "answer": "35"},
            {"question": "5 * 8", "answer": "40"},
            {"question": "5 * 9", "answer": "45"},
            {"question": "5 * 10", "answer": "50"},
            {"question": "5 * 11", "answer": "55"},
            {"question": "5 * 12", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "6 * 1", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "6 * 2", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "6 * 3", "answer": "18"},
            {"question": "6 * 4", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "6 * 5", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "6 * 6", "answer": "36"},
            {"question": "6 * 7", "answer": "42"},
            {"question": "6 * 8", "answer": "48"},
            {"question": "6 * 9", "answer": "54"},
            {"question": "6 * 10", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "6 * 11", "answer": "66"},
            {"question": "6 * 12", "answer": "72"},
            {"question": "7 * 1", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "7 * 2", "answer": "14"},
            {"question": "7 * 3", "answer": "21"},
            {"question": "7 * 4", "answer": "28"},
            {"question": "7 * 5", "answer": "35"},
            {"question": "7 * 6", "answer": "42"},
            {"question": "7 * 7", "answer": "49"},
            {"question": "7 * 8", "answer": "56"},
            {"question": "7 * 9", "answer": "63"},
            {"question": "7 * 10", "answer": "70"},
            {"question": "7 * 11", "answer": "77"},
            {"question": "7 * 12", "answer": "84"},
            {"question": "8 * 1", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "8 * 2", "answer": "16"},
            {"question": "8 * 3", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "8 * 4", "answer": "32"},
            {"question": "8 * 5", "answer": "40"},
            {"question": "8 * 6", "answer": "48"},
            {"question": "8 * 7", "answer": "56"},
            {"question": "8 * 8", "answer": "64"},
            {"question": "8 * 9", "answer": "72"},
            {"question": "8 * 10", "answer": "80"},
            {"question": "8 * 11", "answer": "88"},
            {"question": "8 * 12", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "9 * 1", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "9 * 2", "answer": "18"},
            {"question": "9 * 3", "answer": "27"},
            {"question": "9 * 4", "answer": "36"},
            {"question": "9 * 5", "answer": "45"},
            {"question": "9 * 6", "answer": "54"},
            {"question": "9 * 7", "answer": "63"},
            {"question": "9 * 8", "answer": "72"},
            {"question": "9 * 9", "answer": "81"},
            {"question": "9 * 10", "answer": "90"},
            {"question": "9 * 11", "answer": "99"},
            {"question": "9 * 12", "answer": "108"},
            {"question": "10 * 1", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "10 * 2", "answer": "20"},
            {"question": "10 * 3", "answer": "30"},
            {"question": "10 * 4", "answer": "40"},
            {"question": "10 * 5", "answer": "50"},
            {"question": "10 * 6", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "10 * 7", "answer": "70"},
            {"question": "10 * 8", "answer": "80"},
            {"question": "10 * 9", "answer": "90"},
            {"question": "10 * 10", "answer": "100"},
            {"question": "10 * 11", "answer": "110"},
            {"question": "10 * 12", "answer": "120"},
            {"question": "11 * 1", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "11 * 2", "answer": "22"},
            {"question": "11 * 3", "answer": "33"},
            {"question": "11 * 4", "answer": "44"},
            {"question": "11 * 5", "answer": "55"},
            {"question": "11 * 6", "answer": "66"},
            {"question": "11 * 7", "answer": "77"},
            {"question": "11 * 8", "answer": "88"},
            {"question": "11 * 9", "answer": "99"},
            {"question": "11 * 10", "answer": "110"},
            {"question": "11 * 11", "answer": "121"},
            {"question": "11 * 12", "answer": "132"},
            {"question": "12 * 1", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "12 * 2", "answer": "24"},
            {"question": "12 * 3", "answer": "36"},
            {"question": "12 * 4", "answer": "48"},
            {"question": "12 * 5", "answer": "60"},
            {"question": "12 * 6", "answer": "72"},
            {"question": "12 * 7", "answer": "84"},
            {"question": "12 * 8", "answer": "96"},
            {"question": "12 * 9", "answer": "108"},
            {"question": "12 * 10", "answer": "120"},
            {"question": "12 * 11", "answer": "132"},
            {"question": "12 * 12", "answer": "144"},
            {"question": "1 / 1", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "2 / 1", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "3 / 1", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "4 / 1", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "5 / 1", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "6 / 1", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "7 / 1", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "8 / 1", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "9 / 1", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "10 / 1", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "11 / 1", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "12 / 1", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "2 / 2", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "4 / 2", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "6 / 2", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "8 / 2", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "10 / 2", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "12 / 2", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "14 / 2", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "16 / 2", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "18 / 2", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "20 / 2", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "22 / 2", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "24 / 2", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "3 / 3", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "6 / 3", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "9 / 3", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "12 / 3", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "15 / 3", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "18 / 3", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "21 / 3", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "24 / 3", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "27 / 3", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "30 / 3", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "33 / 3", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "36 / 3", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "4 / 4", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "8 / 4", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "12 / 4", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "16 / 4", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "20 / 4", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "24 / 4", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "28 / 4", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "32 / 4", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "36 / 4", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "40 / 4", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "44 / 4", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "48 / 4", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "5 / 5", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "10 / 5", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "15 / 5", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "20 / 5", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "25 / 5", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "30 / 5", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "35 / 5", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "40 / 5", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "45 / 5", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "50 / 5", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "55 / 5", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "60 / 5", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "6 / 6", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "12 / 6", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "18 / 6", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "24 / 6", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "30 / 6", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "36 / 6", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "42 / 6", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "48 / 6", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "54 / 6", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "60 / 6", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "66 / 6", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "72 / 6", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "7 / 7", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "14 / 7", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "21 / 7", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "28 / 7", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "35 / 7", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "42 / 7", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "49 / 7", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "56 / 7", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "63 / 7", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "70 / 7", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "77 / 7", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "84 / 7", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "8 / 8", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "16 / 8", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "24 / 8", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "32 / 8", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "40 / 8", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "48 / 8", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "56 / 8", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "64 / 8", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "72 / 8", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "80 / 8", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "88 / 8", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "96 / 8", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "9 / 9", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "18 / 9", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "27 / 9", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "36 / 9", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "45 / 9", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "54 / 9", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "63 / 9", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "72 / 9", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "81 / 9", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "90 / 9", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "99 / 9", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "108 / 9", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "10 / 10", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "20 / 10", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "30 / 10", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "40 / 10", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "50 / 10", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "60 / 10", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "70 / 10", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "80 / 10", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "90 / 10", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "100 / 10", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "110 / 10", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "120 / 10", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "11 / 11", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "22 / 11", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "33 / 11", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "44 / 11", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "55 / 11", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "66 / 11", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "77 / 11", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "88 / 11", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "99 / 11", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "110 / 11", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "121 / 11", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "132 / 11", "answer": "12"},
            {"question": "12 / 12", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "24 / 12", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "36 / 12", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "48 / 12", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "60 / 12", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "72 / 12", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "84 / 12", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "96 / 12", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "108 / 12", "answer": "9"},
            {"question": "120 / 12", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "132 / 12", "answer": "11"},
            {"question": "144 / 12", "answer": "12"},
        ],
    },
    {
        "grade": 4,
        "questions": [
            {"question": "²/₃ + ⁴/₉", "answer": "10/9"},
            {"question": "²/₉ + ¹/₃", "answer": "5/9"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ + ⁵/₆", "answer": "5/2"},
            {"question": "³/₅ + ⁶/₅", "answer": "9/5"},
            {"question": "⁵/₄ + ¹/₂", "answer": "7/4"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ⁴/₅", "answer": "13/10"},
            {"question": "²/₃ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "7/3"},
            {"question": "⁵/₉ + ⁴/₃", "answer": "17/9"},
            {"question": "⁷/₃ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "³/₈ + ⁵/₈", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "³/₂ + ⁷/₆", "answer": "8/3"},
            {"question": "⁵/₆ + ⁷/₆", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₀ + ²/₅", "answer": "11/10"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₁ + ¹⁰/₁₁", "answer": "17/11"},
            {"question": "³/₂ + ⁷/₄", "answer": "13/4"},
            {"question": "⁵/₉ + ²/₉", "answer": "7/9"},
            {"question": "⁵/₉ + ⁷/₉", "answer": "4/3"},
            {"question": "²/₅ + ²/₅", "answer": "4/5"},
            {"question": "³/₇ + ⁶/₇", "answer": "9/7"},
            {"question": "²/₅ + ⁷/₅", "answer": "9/5"},
            {"question": "¹/₆ + ³/₄", "answer": "11/12"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ + ⁵/₂", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ + ³/₈", "answer": "7/4"},
            {"question": "³/₂ + ³/₄", "answer": "9/4"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ³/₁₀", "answer": "4/5"},
            {"question": "¹²/₇ + ⁴/₇", "answer": "16/7"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ³/₄", "answer": "5/4"},
            {"question": "⁸/₁₁ + ⁸/₁₁", "answer": "16/11"},
            {"question": "⁹/₈ + ³/₄", "answer": "15/8"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₀ + ¹/₂", "answer": "8/5"},
            {"question": "⁴/₁₁ + ⁷/₁₁", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ + ⁵/₆", "answer": "7/6"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ³/₂", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₇ + ¹²/₇", "answer": "22/7"},
            {"question": "²/₃ + ⁴/₃", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "¹²/₁₁ + ⁸/₁₁", "answer": "20/11"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ + ⁷/₆", "answer": "3/2"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ + ⁸/₃", "answer": "13/3"},
            {"question": "¹²/₁₁ + ³/₁₁", "answer": "15/11"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₀ + ⁹/₁₀", "answer": "9/5"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₃ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "5"},
            {"question": "⁹/₂ + ¹¹/₂", "answer": "10"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₇ + ⁶/₇", "answer": "17/7"},
            {"question": "⁹/₇ + ⁴/₇", "answer": "13/7"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₃ + ¹⁰/₃", "answer": "20/3"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₉ + ²/₉", "answer": "13/9"},
            {"question": "²/₃ + ¹/₆", "answer": "5/6"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ¹¹/₄", "answer": "13/4"},
            {"question": "³/₅ + ²/₅", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "²/₃ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "7/3"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "5/6"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "5/6"},
            {"question": "⁷/₅ - ³/₅", "answer": "4/5"},
            {"question": "³/₁₀ - ¹/₅", "answer": "1/10"},
            {"question": "²/₃ - ¹/₃", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ - ²/₃", "answer": "2/3"},
            {"question": "²/₅ - ¹/₅", "answer": "1/5"},
            {"question": "⁵/₁₂ - ¹/₄", "answer": "1/6"},
            {"question": "¹²/₅ - ⁷/₅", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₁ - ⁴/₁₁", "answer": "5/11"},
            {"question": "²/₃ - ¹/₂", "answer": "1/6"},
            {"question": "⁵/₉ - ¹/₃", "answer": "2/9"},
            {"question": "⁷/₆ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ - ⁴/₇", "answer": "2/7"},
            {"question": "⁷/₃ - ²/₃", "answer": "5/3"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ¹/₄", "answer": "1/4"},
            {"question": "⁷/₉ - ¹/₃", "answer": "4/9"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₀ - ³/₁₀", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "⁹/₂ - ⁵/₂", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ - ⁹/₄", "answer": "1/4"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₂ - ⁷/₁₂", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₉ - ⁸/₉", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "⁴/₅ - ²/₅", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₄ - ³/₂", "answer": "5/4"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₀ - ⁷/₁₀", "answer": "1/5"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₃ - ⁷/₃", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ - ¹/₆", "answer": "1/12"},
            {"question": "⁷/₈ - ³/₄", "answer": "1/8"},
            {"question": "⁷/₃ - ²/₃", "answer": "5/3"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ - ¹/₆", "answer": "1/12"},
            {"question": "⁹/₇ - ⁵/₇", "answer": "4/7"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ - ³/₂", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "⁹/₄ - ¹/₂", "answer": "7/4"},
            {"question": "²/₃ - ¹/₃", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ - ⁹/₅", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "⁸/₁₁ - ³/₁₁", "answer": "5/11"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ - ¹/₂", "answer": "1/8"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₂ - ⁷/₂", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "¹²/₁₁ - ⁵/₁₁", "answer": "7/11"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ - ⁸/₅", "answer": "3/5"},
            {"question": "⁹/₂ - ³/₂", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "⁷/₆ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "1/3"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₁ - ⁵/₁₁", "answer": "2/11"},
            {"question": "⁵/₁₂ - ¹/₆", "answer": "1/4"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ - ⁴/₃", "answer": "4/3"},
            {"question": "⁸/₅ - ³/₅", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "⁹/₅ - ⁷/₅", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ - ⁵/₈", "answer": "3/4"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ - ²/₃", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ - ⁹/₅", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "5/6"},
            {"question": "2.68 + 5.06", "answer": "7.74"},
            {"question": "4.67 + 1.58", "answer": "6.25"},
            {"question": "4.52 + 2.82", "answer": "7.34"},
            {"question": "14.55 + 16.12", "answer": "30.67"},
            {"question": "10.3 + 11.86", "answer": "22.16"},
            {"question": "15.76 + 3.35", "answer": "19.11"},
            {"question": "16.93 + 3.73", "answer": "20.66"},
            {"question": "11.37 + 18.95", "answer": "30.32"},
            {"question": "9.41 + 17.81", "answer": "27.22"},
            {"question": "15.71 + 19.01", "answer": "34.72"},
            {"question": "7.44 + 1.57", "answer": "9.01"},
            {"question": "7.5 + 17.81", "answer": "25.31"},
            {"question": "19.16 + 11.77", "answer": "30.93"},
            {"question": "9.58 + 1.11", "answer": "10.69"},
            {"question": "5.11 + 12.24", "answer": "17.35"},
            {"question": "11.37 + 18.28", "answer": "29.65"},
            {"question": "13.75 + 6.2", "answer": "19.95"},
            {"question": "13.09 + 8.49", "answer": "21.58"},
            {"question": "16.02 + 12.81", "answer": "28.83"},
            {"question": "10.56 + 1.34", "answer": "11.9"},
            {"question": "12.33 + 4.85", "answer": "17.18"},
            {"question": "12.03 + 14.41", "answer": "26.44"},
            {"question": "16.19 + 13.8", "answer": "29.99"},
            {"question": "7.56 + 17.2", "answer": "24.76"},
            {"question": "11.22 + 3.79", "answer": "15.01"},
            {"question": "11.42 + 10.16", "answer": "21.58"},
            {"question": "19.7 + 19.73", "answer": "39.43"},
            {"question": "5.62 + 9.16", "answer": "14.78"},
            {"question": "1.33 + 2.28", "answer": "3.61"},
            {"question": "4.48 + 16.79", "answer": "21.27"},
            {"question": "9.3 + 17.01", "answer": "26.31"},
            {"question": "13.13 + 1.95", "answer": "15.08"},
            {"question": "18.51 + 7.46", "answer": "25.97"},
            {"question": "6.11 + 16.68", "answer": "22.79"},
            {"question": "4.66 + 10.14", "answer": "14.8"},
            {"question": "15.05 + 3.99", "answer": "19.04"},
            {"question": "5.22 + 11.6", "answer": "16.82"},
            {"question": "10.06 + 13.67", "answer": "23.73"},
            {"question": "13.35 + 4.5", "answer": "17.85"},
            {"question": "6.03 + 10.48", "answer": "16.51"},
            {"question": "3.47 + 11.73", "answer": "15.2"},
            {"question": "7.74 + 6.62", "answer": "14.36"},
            {"question": "18.3 + 15.98", "answer": "34.28"},
            {"question": "3.45 + 6.89", "answer": "10.34"},
            {"question": "10.42 + 6.02", "answer": "16.44"},
            {"question": "13.47 + 16.5", "answer": "29.97"},
            {"question": "15.98 + 8.19", "answer": "24.17"},
            {"question": "8.51 + 9.2", "answer": "17.71"},
            {"question": "1.95 + 1.61", "answer": "3.56"},
            {"question": "1.49 + 1.12", "answer": "2.61"},
            {"question": "16.25 - 2.24", "answer": "14.01"},
            {"question": "11.17 - 6.42", "answer": "4.75"},
            {"question": "13.85 - 3.33", "answer": "10.52"},
            {"question": "1.97 - 1.37", "answer": "0.6"},
            {"question": "1.91 - 1.5", "answer": "0.41"},
            {"question": "8.41 - 4.55", "answer": "3.86"},
            {"question": "18.68 - 18.32", "answer": "0.36"},
            {"question": "5.37 - 1.77", "answer": "3.6"},
            {"question": "4.22 - 1.34", "answer": "2.88"},
            {"question": "10.14 - 9.07", "answer": "1.07"},
            {"question": "10.24 - 4.52", "answer": "5.72"},
            {"question": "12.44 - 1.59", "answer": "10.85"},
            {"question": "16.67 - 5.07", "answer": "11.6"},
            {"question": "13.04 - 4.52", "answer": "8.52"},
            {"question": "18.13 - 15.26", "answer": "2.87"},
            {"question": "7.47 - 2.84", "answer": "4.63"},
            {"question": "9.53 - 6.68", "answer": "2.85"},
            {"question": "3.2 - 2.04", "answer": "1.16"},
            {"question": "14.75 - 1.81", "answer": "12.94"},
            {"question": "9.92 - 1.47", "answer": "8.45"},
            {"question": "12.03 - 10.41", "answer": "1.62"},
            {"question": "9.56 - 6.45", "answer": "3.11"},
            {"question": "2.89 - 2.08", "answer": "0.81"},
            {"question": "14.5 - 11.65", "answer": "2.85"},
            {"question": "8.83 - 3.67", "answer": "5.16"},
            {"question": "15.22 - 10.25", "answer": "4.97"},
            {"question": "15.23 - 11.31", "answer": "3.92"},
            {"question": "2.74 - 1.36", "answer": "1.38"},
            {"question": "5.53 - 2.09", "answer": "3.44"},
            {"question": "15.3 - 5.28", "answer": "10.02"},
            {"question": "13.01 - 7.33", "answer": "5.68"},
            {"question": "9.64 - 5.99", "answer": "3.65"},
            {"question": "3.03 - 1.5", "answer": "1.53"},
            {"question": "2.62 - 1.12", "answer": "1.5"},
            {"question": "9.48 - 8.47", "answer": "1.01"},
            {"question": "9.75 - 6.83", "answer": "2.92"},
            {"question": "6.63 - 5.52", "answer": "1.11"},
            {"question": "3.57 - 2.66", "answer": "0.91"},
            {"question": "5.59 - 2.2", "answer": "3.39"},
            {"question": "12.06 - 2.8", "answer": "9.26"},
            {"question": "14.07 - 8.06", "answer": "6.01"},
            {"question": "17.35 - 16.16", "answer": "1.19"},
            {"question": "1.85 - 1.33", "answer": "0.52"},
            {"question": "16.68 - 3.93", "answer": "12.75"},
            {"question": "18.04 - 3.31", "answer": "14.73"},
            {"question": "14.62 - 8.98", "answer": "5.64"},
            {"question": "3.14 - 1.32", "answer": "1.82"},
            {"question": "6.65 - 5.05", "answer": "1.6"},
            {"question": "19.39 - 10.47", "answer": "8.92"},
            {"question": "8.91 - 1.95", "answer": "6.96"},
        ]
    },
    {
        "grade": 5,
        "questions": [
            {"question": "⁴/₃ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "3"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ + ⁴/₇", "answer": "23/28"},
            {"question": "⁹/₈ + ¹¹/₇", "answer": "151/56"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ + ¹/₃", "answer": "5/3"},
            {"question": "³/₁₁ + ³/₁₁", "answer": "6/11"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₇ + ⁷/₁₁", "answer": "170/77"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ⁷/₈", "answer": "11/8"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₃ + ⁸/₅", "answer": "79/15"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₁₁ + ¹/₂", "answer": "31/22"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ⁵/₆", "answer": "4/3"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₃ + ¹¹/₃", "answer": "7"},
            {"question": "⁴/₁₁ + ⁵/₄", "answer": "71/44"},
            {"question": "⁷/₉ + ⁷/₁₂", "answer": "49/36"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ⁵/₉", "answer": "19/18"},
            {"question": "³/₂ + ⁴/₃", "answer": "17/6"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ + ⁹/₁₀", "answer": "123/70"},
            {"question": "²/₃ + ⁹/₂", "answer": "31/6"},
            {"question": "³/₄ + ²/₃", "answer": "17/12"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₇ + ⁷/₄", "answer": "89/28"},
            {"question": "⁴/₁₁ + ³/₂", "answer": "41/22"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₂ + ⁹/₇", "answer": "185/84"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ + ³/₂", "answer": "7/4"},
            {"question": "⁵/₆ + ¹/₃", "answer": "7/6"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₀ + ¹²/₇", "answer": "197/70"},
            {"question": "³/₅ + ¹/₃", "answer": "14/15"},
            {"question": "²/₇ + ³/₂", "answer": "25/14"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₁₁ + ³/₄", "answer": "73/44"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ + ⁸/₁₁", "answer": "119/88"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ + ⁴/₃", "answer": "11/6"},
            {"question": "⁷/₆ + ²/₉", "answer": "25/18"},
            {"question": "³/₁₀ + ⁸/₃", "answer": "89/30"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ + ⁷/₅", "answer": "39/10"},
            {"question": "²/₅ + ⁵/₇", "answer": "39/35"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ + ¹¹/₆", "answer": "19/6"},
            {"question": "⁵/₆ + ¹²/₅", "answer": "97/30"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ + ⁴/₅", "answer": "58/35"},
            {"question": "⁹/₂ + ³/₂", "answer": "6"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₇ + ²/₃", "answer": "44/21"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₀ + ⁶/₅", "answer": "21/10"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ + ⁹/₇", "answer": "122/35"},
            {"question": "²/₅ + ⁸/₁₁", "answer": "62/55"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₉ + ¹/₂", "answer": "31/18"},
            {"question": "⁵/₇ + ¹¹/₇", "answer": "16/7"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ + ²/₅", "answer": "46/15"},
            {"question": "¹²/₇ + ⁵/₃", "answer": "71/21"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ + ³/₂", "answer": "4"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ + ³/₄", "answer": "25/12"},
            {"question": "³/₄ + ³/₄", "answer": "3/2"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ + ¹/₂", "answer": "9/8"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ + ³/₁₁", "answer": "23/44"},
            {"question": "³/₇ - ⁵/₁₂", "answer": "1/84"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₃ - ⁷/₁₂", "answer": "37/12"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ - ³/₂", "answer": "7/6"},
            {"question": "¹²/₅ - ¹¹/₁₀", "answer": "13/10"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ - ²/₅", "answer": "21/10"},
            {"question": "⁷/₄ - ⁵/₄", "answer": "1/2"},
            {"question": "³/₁₁ - ²/₉", "answer": "5/99"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "11/6"},
            {"question": "³/₄ - ²/₁₁", "answer": "25/44"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ - ⁸/₉", "answer": "16/9"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ - ¹/₅", "answer": "1/20"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ¹/₃", "answer": "1/6"},
            {"question": "⁹/₈ - ⁷/₉", "answer": "25/72"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ - ⁶/₅", "answer": "7/40"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ⁴/₉", "answer": "1/18"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ - ³/₄", "answer": "7/12"},
            {"question": "²/₉ - ²/₁₁", "answer": "4/99"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ - ¹/₄", "answer": "29/12"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ - ³/₁₀", "answer": "39/70"},
            {"question": "³/₄ - ⁴/₇", "answer": "5/28"},
            {"question": "³/₂ - ⁵/₆", "answer": "2/3"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₉ - ¹⁰/₁₁", "answer": "20/99"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ - ⁴/₃", "answer": "1/24"},
            {"question": "⁴/₁₁ - ¹/₃", "answer": "1/33"},
            {"question": "⁸/₅ - ⁴/₅", "answer": "4/5"},
            {"question": "⁹/₇ - ¹/₄", "answer": "29/28"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₀ - ²/₉", "answer": "43/90"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ⁴/₉", "answer": "1/18"},
            {"question": "⁷/₃ - ³/₈", "answer": "47/24"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ - ⁵/₇", "answer": "37/56"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ - ²/₁₁", "answer": "52/77"},
            {"question": "²/₃ - ⁴/₁₁", "answer": "10/33"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ - ¹/₃", "answer": "4/3"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ - ¹/₄", "answer": "1/12"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ³/₈", "answer": "1/8"},
            {"question": "⁶/₅ - ¹/₃", "answer": "13/15"},
            {"question": "³/₄ - ⁵/₇", "answer": "1/28"},
            {"question": "²/₃ - ²/₉", "answer": "4/9"},
            {"question": "⁷/₄ - ¹/₄", "answer": "3/2"},
            {"question": "⁹/₈ - ⁶/₁₁", "answer": "51/88"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₇ - ⁶/₁₁", "answer": "68/77"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ - ¹/₆", "answer": "1/6"},
            {"question": "⁹/₅ - ¹/₅", "answer": "8/5"},
            {"question": "⁷/₅ - ⁴/₃", "answer": "1/15"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ - ¹/₄", "answer": "1/12"},
            {"question": "²/₅ - ¹/₃", "answer": "1/15"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ - ⁵/₁₂", "answer": "1/12"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ - ¹¹/₈", "answer": "9/8"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₀ - ¹/₂", "answer": "2/5"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₄ - ³/₄", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ * ¹²/₇", "answer": "30/7"},
            {"question": "³/₄ * ⁵/₉", "answer": "5/12"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₇ * ²/₃", "answer": "20/21"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ * ⁵/₆", "answer": "25/18"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₁ * ³/₁₁", "answer": "21/121"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ * ⁸/₃", "answer": "32/9"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ * ⁵/₈", "answer": "25/64"},
            {"question": "³/₁₁ * ⁴/₉", "answer": "4/33"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₂ * ³/₅", "answer": "11/20"},
            {"question": "¹/₆ * ¹¹/₂", "answer": "11/12"},
            {"question": "⁴/₅ * ³/₁₁", "answer": "12/55"},
            {"question": "²/₉ * ²/₃", "answer": "4/27"},
            {"question": "⁴/₉ * ¹¹/₂", "answer": "22/9"},
            {"question": "⁷/₆ * ⁵/₁₂", "answer": "35/72"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ * ⁷/₆", "answer": "7/12"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ * ²/₉", "answer": "1/9"},
            {"question": "³/₁₀ * ¹¹/₄", "answer": "33/40"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ * ¹¹/₁₂", "answer": "11/24"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₁ * ³/₁₁", "answer": "27/121"},
            {"question": "³/₂ * ⁵/₆", "answer": "5/4"},
            {"question": "⁷/₈ * ⁸/₉", "answer": "7/9"},
            {"question": "¹/₄ * ⁶/₁₁", "answer": "3/22"},
            {"question": "¹²/₅ * ¹/₄", "answer": "3/5"},
            {"question": "³/₁₁ * ³/₁₁", "answer": "9/121"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ * ³/₄", "answer": "15/8"},
            {"question": "³/₅ * ¹¹/₃", "answer": "11/5"},
            {"question": "⁴/₇ * ¹²/₁₁", "answer": "48/77"},
            {"question": "³/₇ * ³/₅", "answer": "9/35"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ * ⁵/₃", "answer": "11/3"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ * ¹²/₇", "answer": "15/14"},
            {"question": "²/₉ * ⁸/₉", "answer": "16/81"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ * ¹²/₇", "answer": "6/7"},
            {"question": "²/₅ * ²/₃", "answer": "4/15"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ * ⁴/₅", "answer": "16/15"},
            {"question": "⁵/₁₁ * ⁷/₁₂", "answer": "35/132"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₄ * ²/₅", "answer": "11/10"},
            {"question": "⁸/₉ * ⁴/₉", "answer": "32/81"},
            {"question": "⁵/₈ * ⁵/₁₂", "answer": "25/96"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₁₀ * ³/₂", "answer": "33/20"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₆ * ⁹/₇", "answer": "33/14"},
            {"question": "³/₄ * ⁹/₄", "answer": "27/16"},
            {"question": "⁵/₁₁ * ⁹/₅", "answer": "9/11"},
            {"question": "⁶/₅ * ⁷/₃", "answer": "14/5"},
            {"question": "⁷/₄ * ⁷/₅", "answer": "49/20"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ * ¹⁰/₁₁", "answer": "40/33"},
            {"question": "⁹/₂ * ⁹/₇", "answer": "81/14"},
            {"question": "⁹/₈ * ²/₃", "answer": "3/4"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ * ³/₈", "answer": "5/8"},
            {"question": "³/₇ * ²/₃", "answer": "2/7"},
            {"question": "³/₄ * ¹²/₅", "answer": "9/5"},
            {"question": "⁵/₄ / ⁵/₃", "answer": "3/4"},
            {"question": "⁵/₁₁ / ⁵/₆", "answer": "6/11"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ / ⁶/₅", "answer": "11/6"},
            {"question": "⁶/₁₁ / ⁷/₃", "answer": "18/77"},
            {"question": "⁶/₅ / ¹¹/₃", "answer": "18/55"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ / ³/₂", "answer": "8/9"},
            {"question": "²/₃ / ⁷/₁₀", "answer": "20/21"},
            {"question": "¹/₆ / ⁵/₄", "answer": "2/15"},
            {"question": "³/₈ / ⁹/₇", "answer": "7/24"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ / ²/₅", "answer": "5/4"},
            {"question": "⁶/₅ / ¹⁰/₃", "answer": "9/25"},
            {"question": "⁵/₇ / ⁸/₁₁", "answer": "55/56"},
            {"question": "⁷/₁₀ / ¹/₂", "answer": "7/5"},
            {"question": "¹²/₁₁ / ¹¹/₇", "answer": "84/121"},
            {"question": "¹²/₅ / ⁵/₇", "answer": "84/25"},
            {"question": "⁵/₂ / ⁹/₈", "answer": "20/9"},
            {"question": "¹/₃ / ¹²/₇", "answer": "7/36"},
            {"question": "¹/₅ / ¹⁰/₇", "answer": "7/50"},
            {"question": "³/₇ / ³/₄", "answer": "4/7"},
            {"question": "⁹/₅ / ⁹/₈", "answer": "8/5"},
            {"question": "¹/₅ / ⁹/₅", "answer": "1/9"},
            {"question": "⁴/₅ / ¹/₆", "answer": "24/5"},
            {"question": "⁷/₆ / ¹/₃", "answer": "7/2"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₅ / ⁸/₇", "answer": "77/40"},
            {"question": "⁷/₃ / ⁹/₁₀", "answer": "70/27"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ / ⁹/₅", "answer": "10/21"},
            {"question": "³/₅ / ⁵/₁₁", "answer": "33/25"},
            {"question": "⁵/₉ / ⁸/₇", "answer": "35/72"},
            {"question": "⁴/₅ / ⁵/₂", "answer": "8/25"},
            {"question": "⁷/₄ / ⁹/₇", "answer": "49/36"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₁₁ / ⁵/₇", "answer": "14/11"},
            {"question": "⁹/₁₁ / ⁷/₁₀", "answer": "90/77"},
            {"question": "⁸/₉ / ⁴/₃", "answer": "2/3"},
            {"question": "⁶/₇ / ⁹/₄", "answer": "8/21"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ / ³/₂", "answer": "10/9"},
            {"question": "¹²/₁₁ / ³/₂", "answer": "8/11"},
            {"question": "⁴/₇ / ¹¹/₂", "answer": "8/77"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ / ⁴/₃", "answer": "1"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₈ / ³/₂", "answer": "11/12"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ / ¹/₄", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "⁴/₃ / ²/₃", "answer": "2"},
            {"question": "¹/₂ / ¹⁰/₃", "answer": "3/20"},
            {"question": "³/₅ / ⁴/₁₁", "answer": "33/20"},
            {"question": "⁸/₁₁ / ³/₅", "answer": "40/33"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₉ / ⁵/₂", "answer": "22/45"},
            {"question": "¹¹/₆ / ⁷/₁₀", "answer": "55/21"},
            {"question": "⁸/₃ / ¹/₃", "answer": "8"},
            {"question": "⁵/₃ / ⁹/₁₀", "answer": "50/27"},
            {"question": "³/₂ / ⁶/₅", "answer": "5/4"},
            {"question": "¹⁰/₃ / ¹¹/₁₀", "answer": "100/33"},{"question": "44.314 + 13.275", "answer": "57.589"},
            {"question": "55.553 + 40.407", "answer": "95.96"},
            {"question": "85.001 + 58.634", "answer": "143.635"},
            {"question": "88.653 + 70.835", "answer": "159.488"},
            {"question": "25.23 + 82.525", "answer": "107.755"},
            {"question": "67.865 + 43.947", "answer": "111.812"},
            {"question": "84.731 + 92.459", "answer": "177.19"},
            {"question": "60.286 + 54.495", "answer": "114.781"},
            {"question": "20.182 + 2.247", "answer": "22.429"},
            {"question": "19.377 + 95.659", "answer": "115.036"},
            {"question": "58.661 + 98.506", "answer": "157.167"},
            {"question": "34.916 + 12.684", "answer": "47.6"},
            {"question": "29.345 + 21.721", "answer": "51.066"},
            {"question": "45.935 + 1.03", "answer": "46.965"},
            {"question": "10.037 + 48.232", "answer": "58.269"},
            {"question": "54.97 + 3.6", "answer": "58.57"},
            {"question": "59.308 + 24.907", "answer": "84.215"},
            {"question": "90.654 + 22.236", "answer": "112.89"},
            {"question": "70.152 + 13.919", "answer": "84.071"},
            {"question": "54.514 + 57.41", "answer": "111.924"},
            {"question": "26.598 + 12.086", "answer": "38.684"},
            {"question": "39.909 + 37.545", "answer": "77.454"},
            {"question": "33.547 + 71.667", "answer": "105.214"},
            {"question": "55.617 + 50.707", "answer": "106.324"},
            {"question": "75.671 + 93.111", "answer": "168.782"},
            {"question": "77.244 + 10.326", "answer": "87.57"},
            {"question": "73.835 + 10.842", "answer": "84.677"},
            {"question": "2.99 + 44.525", "answer": "47.515"},
            {"question": "59.597 + 87.354", "answer": "146.951"},
            {"question": "12.925 + 78.816", "answer": "91.741"},
            {"question": "79.8 + 74.363", "answer": "154.163"},
            {"question": "78.076 + 30.898", "answer": "108.974"},
            {"question": "12.283 + 39.217", "answer": "51.5"},
            {"question": "6.951 + 38.031", "answer": "44.982"},
            {"question": "82.291 + 78.21", "answer": "160.501"},
            {"question": "74.118 + 88.589", "answer": "162.707"},
            {"question": "58.728 + 65.621", "answer": "124.349"},
            {"question": "36.717 + 71.348", "answer": "108.065"},
            {"question": "84.162 + 36.417", "answer": "120.579"},
            {"question": "54.7 + 34.962", "answer": "89.662"},
            {"question": "86.728 + 25.175", "answer": "111.903"},
            {"question": "80.258 + 28.553", "answer": "108.811"},
            {"question": "2.642 + 8.817", "answer": "11.459"},
            {"question": "44.354 + 96.428", "answer": "140.782"},
            {"question": "58.787 + 18.948", "answer": "77.735"},
            {"question": "8.024 + 91.946", "answer": "99.97"},
            {"question": "5.291 + 14.257", "answer": "19.548"},
            {"question": "58.065 + 74.019", "answer": "132.084"},
            {"question": "70.41 + 23.534", "answer": "93.944"},
            {"question": "26.724 + 87.721", "answer": "114.445"},
            {"question": "52.333 - 49.188", "answer": "3.145"},
            {"question": "71.881 - 69.688", "answer": "2.193"},
            {"question": "27.819 - 15.177", "answer": "12.642"},
            {"question": "30.865 - 30.391", "answer": "0.474"},
            {"question": "19.642 - 19.048", "answer": "0.594"},
            {"question": "97.173 - 73.392", "answer": "23.781"},
            {"question": "67.968 - 35.064", "answer": "32.904"},
            {"question": "7.929 - 3.021", "answer": "4.908"},
            {"question": "76.266 - 38.101", "answer": "38.165"},
            {"question": "78.307 - 11.861", "answer": "66.446"},
            {"question": "90.257 - 78.752", "answer": "11.505"},
            {"question": "8.823 - 7.235", "answer": "1.588"},
            {"question": "61.979 - 10.881", "answer": "51.098"},
            {"question": "51.105 - 45", "answer": "6.105"},
            {"question": "43.619 - 33.205", "answer": "10.414"},
            {"question": "52.443 - 37.965", "answer": "14.478"},
            {"question": "65.596 - 10.549", "answer": "55.047"},
            {"question": "52.54 - 12.451", "answer": "40.089"},
            {"question": "29.924 - 24.198", "answer": "5.726"},
            {"question": "45.773 - 26.362", "answer": "19.411"},
            {"question": "67.216 - 64.245", "answer": "2.971"},
            {"question": "64.134 - 46.191", "answer": "17.943"},
            {"question": "94.74 - 24.417", "answer": "70.323"},
            {"question": "2.859 - 1.941", "answer": "0.918"},
            {"question": "22.745 - 20.292", "answer": "2.453"},
            {"question": "69.783 - 45.061", "answer": "24.722"},
            {"question": "26.254 - 18.059", "answer": "8.195"},
            {"question": "98.148 - 9.33", "answer": "88.818"},
            {"question": "14.787 - 3.44", "answer": "11.347"},
            {"question": "70.795 - 24.911", "answer": "45.884"},
            {"question": "94.37 - 93.349", "answer": "1.021"},
            {"question": "65.047 - 38.647", "answer": "26.4"},
            {"question": "71.223 - 56.141", "answer": "15.082"},
            {"question": "15.844 - 8.584", "answer": "7.26"},
            {"question": "12.818 - 11.888", "answer": "0.93"},
            {"question": "69.463 - 63.4", "answer": "6.063"},
            {"question": "78.984 - 56.485", "answer": "22.499"},
            {"question": "6.869 - 5.634", "answer": "1.235"},
            {"question": "43.887 - 34.213", "answer": "9.674"},
            {"question": "23.949 - 1.942", "answer": "22.007"},
            {"question": "7.425 - 3.068", "answer": "4.357"},
            {"question": "50.106 - 37.77", "answer": "12.336"},
            {"question": "26.665 - 10.726", "answer": "15.939"},
            {"question": "40.373 - 5.741", "answer": "34.632"},
            {"question": "46.02 - 26.925", "answer": "19.095"},
            {"question": "4.872 - 1.777", "answer": "3.095"},
            {"question": "34.897 - 18.733", "answer": "16.164"},
            {"question": "27.284 - 15.254", "answer": "12.03"},
            {"question": "81.34 - 30.406", "answer": "50.934"},
            {"question": "36 - 2.868", "answer": "33.132"},
            {"question": "7.7 * 6.85", "answer": "52.745"},
            {"question": "2.4 * 3.74", "answer": "8.976"},
            {"question": "8.97 * 4.1", "answer": "36.777"},
            {"question": "4.91 * 2.67", "answer": "13.1097"},
            {"question": "2.75 * 1.67", "answer": "4.5925"},
            {"question": "9.85 * 8.2", "answer": "80.77"},
            {"question": "7.21 * 4.71", "answer": "33.9591"},
            {"question": "6.01 * 7.76", "answer": "46.6376"},
            {"question": "5.49 * 2.62", "answer": "14.3838"},
            {"question": "3.2 * 5.13", "answer": "16.416"},
            {"question": "9.89 * 9.1", "answer": "89.999"},
            {"question": "8.38 * 1.9", "answer": "15.922"},
            {"question": "2.81 * 5.78", "answer": "16.2418"},
            {"question": "2.32 * 1.73", "answer": "4.0136"},
            {"question": "6.67 * 7.51", "answer": "50.0917"},
            {"question": "7.62 * 4.64", "answer": "35.3568"},
            {"question": "7.94 * 6.69", "answer": "53.1186"},
            {"question": "4.8 * 6.11", "answer": "29.328"},
            {"question": "4.49 * 3.42", "answer": "15.3558"},
            {"question": "2.58 * 2.21", "answer": "5.7018"},
            {"question": "3.42 * 2.91", "answer": "9.9522"},
            {"question": "5.39 * 4.65", "answer": "25.0635"},
            {"question": "9.19 * 4", "answer": "36.76"},
            {"question": "5 * 1.76", "answer": "8.8"},
            {"question": "6.98 * 2.34", "answer": "16.3332"},
            {"question": "2.14 * 4.94", "answer": "10.5716"},
            {"question": "6.44 * 2.8", "answer": "18.032"},
            {"question": "8.56 * 8.98", "answer": "76.8688"},
            {"question": "4.11 * 4.85", "answer": "19.9335"},
            {"question": "8.79 * 5.04", "answer": "44.3016"},
            {"question": "2.92 * 7.93", "answer": "23.1556"},
            {"question": "9.33 * 4.97", "answer": "46.3701"},
            {"question": "9.61 * 2.54", "answer": "24.4094"},
            {"question": "4.69 * 2.54", "answer": "11.9126"},
            {"question": "4.87 * 9.51", "answer": "46.3137"},
            {"question": "3.19 * 3.78", "answer": "12.0582"},
            {"question": "4.03 * 7.81", "answer": "31.4743"},
            {"question": "1.67 * 7.03", "answer": "11.7401"},
            {"question": "7.39 * 8.55", "answer": "63.1845"},
            {"question": "9.57 * 7.75", "answer": "74.1675"},
            {"question": "7.12 * 6.19", "answer": "44.0728"},
            {"question": "9.77 * 2.74", "answer": "26.7698"},
            {"question": "6.58 * 2.53", "answer": "16.6474"},
            {"question": "9.63 * 1.84", "answer": "17.7192"},
            {"question": "8.3 * 1.59", "answer": "13.197"},
            {"question": "9.87 * 7.04", "answer": "69.4848"},
            {"question": "3.64 * 3.17", "answer": "11.5388"},
            {"question": "5.68 * 7.34", "answer": "41.6912"},
            {"question": "6.96 * 8.04", "answer": "55.9584"},
            {"question": "1.64 * 7.98", "answer": "13.0872"},
            {"question": "52.8557 / 9.77", "answer": "5.41"},
            {"question": "26.0832 / 5.28", "answer": "4.94"},
            {"question": "10.34 / 2.75", "answer": "3.76"},
            {"question": "5.5669 / 3.11", "answer": "1.79"},
            {"question": "29.1401 / 6.49", "answer": "4.49"},
            {"question": "30.4668 / 5.58", "answer": "5.46"},
            {"question": "6.5065 / 1.43", "answer": "4.55"},
            {"question": "9.3233 / 1.33", "answer": "7.01"},
            {"question": "36.7284 / 7.23", "answer": "5.08"},
            {"question": "30.745 / 4.3", "answer": "7.15"},
            {"question": "36.8672 / 5.62", "answer": "6.56"},
            {"question": "22.4655 / 8.81", "answer": "2.55"},
            {"question": "13.2132 / 2.73", "answer": "4.84"},
            {"question": "13.0858 / 7.19", "answer": "1.82"},
            {"question": "89.3547 / 9.09", "answer": "9.83"},
            {"question": "11.2233 / 6.27", "answer": "1.79"},
            {"question": "40.762 / 9.16", "answer": "4.45"},
            {"question": "5.217 / 2.35", "answer": "2.22"},
            {"question": "52.4552 / 9.52", "answer": "5.51"},
            {"question": "85.0704 / 8.88", "answer": "9.58"},
            {"question": "72.6144 / 7.32", "answer": "9.92"},
            {"question": "35.5122 / 5.43", "answer": "6.54"},
            {"question": "37.4904 / 3.81", "answer": "9.84"},
            {"question": "45.792 / 6.36", "answer": "7.2"},
            {"question": "9.6492 / 1.32", "answer": "7.31"},
            {"question": "11.6739 / 3.57", "answer": "3.27"},
            {"question": "8.3366 / 5.71", "answer": "1.46"},
            {"question": "19.9528 / 5.09", "answer": "3.92"},
            {"question": "13.0834 / 6.26", "answer": "2.09"},
            {"question": "11.0889 / 3.33", "answer": "3.33"},
            {"question": "24.6312 / 6.22", "answer": "3.96"},
            {"question": "4.3754 / 1.67", "answer": "2.62"},
            {"question": "13.3424 / 4.96", "answer": "2.69"},
            {"question": "9.6514 / 9.02", "answer": "1.07"},
            {"question": "60.3668 / 8.93", "answer": "6.76"},
            {"question": "28.6062 / 8.34", "answer": "3.43"},
            {"question": "17.2832 / 9.82", "answer": "1.76"},
            {"question": "49.4375 / 6.25", "answer": "7.91"},
            {"question": "5.0874 / 3.66", "answer": "1.39"},
            {"question": "48.4872 / 5.34", "answer": "9.08"},
            {"question": "21.735 / 5.75", "answer": "3.78"},
            {"question": "30.4024 / 4.88", "answer": "6.23"},
            {"question": "46.8791 / 8.21", "answer": "5.71"},
            {"question": "12.0624 / 3.36", "answer": "3.59"},
            {"question": "20.4768 / 6.32", "answer": "3.24"},
            {"question": "6.923 / 3.22", "answer": "2.15"},
            {"question": "15.1348 / 9.64", "answer": "1.57"},
            {"question": "23.4069 / 4.51", "answer": "5.19"},
            {"question": "4.2315 / 1.05", "answer": "4.03"},
            {"question": "35.8559 / 3.67", "answer": "9.77"},
        ],
    },
]
